/*quiz_data9 */

const questions = [
    {
//704問目
question:"image(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["ドレス","絵、像","試みる","スピーチ"],
correctAnswer: "絵、像"
    },
    {
//713問目
question:"production(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["ほとんど","首都","生産","易しい、単純な"],
correctAnswer: "生産"
    },
    {
//728問目
question:"clearly(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["昨日","生産","部門","はっきりと"],
correctAnswer: "はっきりと"
    },
    {
//736問目
question:"department(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["競争","部門","前向きな","キャリア"],
correctAnswer: "部門"
    },
    {
//741問目
question:"board(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["経営者、管理者、部長","板","さまざまな","選択"],
correctAnswer: "板"
    },
    {
//756問目
question:"analysis(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["分析","窓","仕事","申し込む"],
correctAnswer: "分析"
    },
    {
//766問目
question:"challenge(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["必要","下に","異議を申し立てる","識別する"],
correctAnswer: "異議を申し立てる"
    },
    {
//779問目
question:"ability(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["能力","にもかかわらず","応募書","映画"],
correctAnswer: "能力"
    },
    {
//786問目
question:"release(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["下に","釈放する","含む","触る"],
correctAnswer: "釈放する"
    },
    {
//793問目
question:"fear(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["酒場","恐れ","プレーヤー","スピーチ"],
correctAnswer: "恐れ"
    }
];

export default questions;

